Guide to the Herman Haupt Chapman Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE AND TOPICAL FILES, 1897-1963; Series II; 16 linear feet (39 boxes)
  - Volume of seed trees, 1937, 1939, undated (Box 89, Folder 959)
  - Vredenburgh, Sellers H., 1950, 1952 (Box 89, Folder 960)
  - Wackerman trip: photographs and list, undated (Box 89, Folder 961)
  - Wadsworth, Frank H., 1940 (Box 89, Folder 962)
  - Wagar, J. V. K., 1951-1956, undated (Box 89, Folder 963-964)
  - Wahlenberg, William G., 1955, undated (Box 89, Folder 965-966)
  - Walcott, Frederick C., 1933 (Box 89, Folder 967)
  - Water erosion, undated (Box 89, Folder 968)
  - Weaver, Harold, 1951 (Box 89, Folder 969)
  - Weeks law, 1907-1932 (Box 89, Folder 970-971)
  - Weights, undated (Box 89, Folder 972)
  - West Virginia songs, 1947 (Box 90, Folder 973)
  - Western yellow pine, 1913-1948 (Box 90, Folder 974-982)
  - Wilderness areas and Wilderness Society, 1940-1959 (Box 90, Folder 983-984)
  - Wildlife Society
    See: box 77, folder 671
  - Willets, Robert T., 1947 (Box 90, Folder 985)
  - Williamson, B. F., 1946, 1949 (Box 91, Folder 986)
  - Wilson, F. G.: height and thinning, 1950 (Box 91, Folder 987)
  - Winer, Herb, 1953 (Box 91, Folder 988)
  - Wiseman, Louise, 1927 (Box 91, Folder 989)
  - Wiseman, Robert L., 1927 (Box 91, Folder 990)
  - Wolfe, Robert E., 1948-1952, undated (Box 91, Folder 991)
  - Wood poles, undated (Box 91, Folder 992)
  - Woodman, C. L., 1951 (Box 91, Folder 993)
  - Woods, Ed, 1949-1951, undated (Box 91, Folder 994)
  - Woodward, Harry K., 1956 (Box 91, Folder 995)
  - Work, Herman, 1950-1953, undated (Box 91, Folder 996-997)
  - Wotterington, Norman, 1951 (Box 91, Folder 998)
  - W. T. Smith Area, Alabama, 1948-1951 (Box 91, Folder 999)
  - Wyman, Edgar P., 1948 (Box 91, Folder 1000)
  - Yale Forestry School
    See also: box 54, folders 165-198 box 55, folder 205 box 58, folder 297 box 60, folders 334-335 box 86, folder 890
    - Alumni
      - Employment status, 1954 (Box 91, Folder 1001)
      - Photographs, 1917-1920, undated (Box 91, Folder 1002)
      - Roll, 1951-1959 (Box 91, Folder 1003)
    - Faculty photographs, undated (Box 91, Folder 1004)
    - Fellowships, 1955 (Box 91, Folder 1005)
    - Fiftieth anniversary, 1950 (Box 91, Folder 1006)
    - Gradebooks
      See: box 60, folders 334-335
    - Photographs, undated (Box 91, Folder 1007)
    - Seminars, 1955, undated (Box 91, Folder 1008)
    - Songs, 1942 (Box 91, Folder 1009)
  - Yale Forestry School News, 1917-1933 (Box 91, Folder 1010)
  - Yield tables, 1905-1931 (Box 91, Folder 1011-1015)
  - Yield tables, 1903-1939 (Box 92, Folder 1016-1027)
    See also: box 89, folder 959
  - Zon, R., 1921 (Box 92, Folder 1028)
  - Unidentified, 1956, undated (Box 92, Folder 1029)
- PHOTOGRAPHS, 1905-1947; Series III; 1.75' (5 boxes)
  Series III is arranged in three sections: Professional; Personal; Oversize.
  - Professional
    - Alabama, 1915, 1931 (Box 93)
      See also: box 89, folder 961
    - Alumni, undated (Box 93)
      See also: box 89, folder 957
      See also: box 91, folder 1002
    - Alumni and camps, undated (Box 93)
      See also: box 91, folder 1007
      See also: box 96
    - Arkansas
      - General, 1937 (Box 93)
      - Camp, 1913 (Box 93)
      - Crossett Lumber Company, 1923-1947 (Box 93)
      - Wilmar, 1933 (Box 93)
    - Arizona
      - Coconino National Forest, 1917-1919; 1939 (Box 93)
      - Grand Canyon, 1917 (Box 93)
      - Manzano, 1918 (Box 93)
      - Ponderosa Pine, 1932 (Box 93)
      - Scenery, 1918 (Box 93)
      - Sitgreaves, 1917 (Box 93)
      - Tusayan National Forest, 1917-1918 (Box 93)
    - British
      - Buildings, undated (Box 93)
      - Government plantations, undated (Box 93)
      - Estate forestry, 1936 (Box 93)
      - Scenery, undated (Box 93)
      - Woodlands, 1936 (Box 93)
    - California
      - General, undated (Box 93)
      - Plunias National Forest, 1912 (Box 93)
    - Camps, 1922 (Box 93)
    - Class of 1926, undated (Box 93)
    - Colorado, 1932-1939 (Box 93)
    - D-3, 1917-1918 (Box 93)
    - Douglas fir, 1932 (Box 94)
    - Grazing
      See: box 45, folder 138
    - Idaho, 1912 (Box 94)
    - Illinois, 1922 (Box 94)
    - Indiana Forest Reserve, undated (Box 94)
    - Longleaf pine, undated (Box 94)
      See also: box 43, folder 129
    - Louisiana oil boom, undated (Box 94)
    - Michigan, 1923 (Box 94)
    - Minnesota
      - General, 1905 (Box 94)
      - Backus trip, 1923 (Box 94)
      - Cass Lake, 1932, 1937 (Box 94)
      - Chippewa National Forest, 1927 (Box 94)
      - Cloquet experiment, 1916 (Box 94)
      - Grand Rapids, 1916-1932 (Box 94)
      - National forest, 1916 (Box 94)
      - Norway Beach
        See: box 33, folder 96
      - Norway Pine, 1906 (Box 94)
    - Mississippi, 1914 (Box 94)
    - Montana: Deerlodge National Forest, 1912 (Box 95)
    - National forest, 1912 (Box 95)
    - Nebraska, 1937 (Box 95)
    - Nevada, 1912 (Box 95)
    - New Mexico, 1916-1937 (Box 95)
    - North Carolina, 1916 (Box 95)
    - Northern hardwoods, 1935 (Box 95)
    - Southern camps, undated (Box 95)
    - Union, 1933 (Box 95)
    - Urania, Louisiana (Box 95)
      See also: box 78, folder 713
      See also: box 87, folder 902
      See also: box 87, folder 909
      See also: box 89, folder 946
    - Virginia, 1931 (Box 96)
    - Washington, undated (Box 96)
    - Wisconsin: Menominee, 1945-1946 (Box 96)
    - Yale forestry camp, undated (Box 96)
    - Yale Forestry School
      See: box 91, folder 1004
      See: box 98
    - Unidentified, 1916-1923, undated (Box 96)
  - Personal
    See also: box 70, folder 494
    - Alger-Sullivan Company, undated (Box 97)
    - Groups, undated (Box 97)
    - Inventories, undated (Box 97)
    - New Zealand, undated (Box 97)
      See also: box 77, folders 679-680
    - Portraits, undated (Box 97)
    - Miscellanea, undated (Box 97)
    - Undated (Box 97)
  - Oversize (Folio), undated (Box 98)